:
* Temptation *
DRIVER :
* Temptation and sin *
* Were my closest friends... *
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Turn left in 100 feet.
* So cold and alone... *
Turn left in 50 feet.
-* I heard about you, sinner *
-AUTOMATED VOICE: Turn left.
Recalculating.
Was it a left back there?
Yeah, I think so.
J-Just follow the GPS,
I'm in a hurry.
Oh, I don't listen to the GPS.
-No way.
-AUTOMATED VOICE: Turn left.
It's always wrong--
is there another way?
Why does it keep
saying "a left"?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Recalculating.
I've never been
to this place before,
so just-just follow the GPS.
DRIVER:
This thing is crazy.
Right?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Turn left in 500 feet.
* Yeah *
* I want to walk in the way *
* My precious savior... *
(Alfred and Christian
speaking indistinctly)
EARN:
Sorry.
Sit right here.
-Hey, you must be Earn.
-Yes.
Come on in. Have a seat.
-Um... hey.
Sorry I'm late. Um...
My Lyft driver
w-was... religious.
It's fine.
Alfred just got in here.
-You brought a baby.
-Had to.
-LOTTIE: I ain't a baby.
CHRISTIAN: So, gentlemen,
I understand you're looking
-for an entertainment lawyer.
-Yes. Yes, we are.
Well, let me tell you a little
about myself first.
I'm from the D.C. area,
near U Street.
I graduated from Howard
and then went to Georgetown,
but I'm definitely a Hoyas fan.
I graduated the top ten
of my class, and after school,
I went to work at
the Lance and Roberts Law Firm
for almost ten years.
-* Nah-nah nah-nah-nah-nah *
* Nah-nah-nah *
* Nah-nah nah-nah-nah-nah
nah-nah-nah, nah-nah-nah... *
...been here in Atlanta
for the past five years, now.
So who are some of the people
you represent, man?
Well, I represent some singers
and some rappers.
I represent the rapper A.V.
Oh, okay.
-Y-You know that dude.
-Yeah, that dude.
-He had that one song,
"Program." Yeah.
-* Program * Yeah.
CHRISTIAN:
I also represent some actors.
I have four clients on Love &
Hip Hop: Atlanta right now.
LOTTIE:
I don't like lemons.
Yes, I know. You hate lemons.
If he was to go with you,
what would that take?
Well, um, just a few signatures,
and I would receive five percent
of any deal
I looked over for you.
Five percent?
Yes, but that's the standard
that any lawyer would charge.
Look, man. I just don't
want no janky-ass lawyer
putting his hands on my
contracts and checks, a'ight?
I want, like,
a high-level Jewish dude,
not somebody gonna rob me
like Don King or some shit.
Man, Don King wasn't a lawyer,
I'm pretty sure.
Also, Christian came
highly recommended.
He-He supposedly does good work.
Recommended by who, man?
He ain't even got no clients
that make actual money.
All he got is some
F-level rappers
and some reality TV stars.
Reality TV stars, Earn.
Just find me, like,
a big-level firm, man.
Jewish dude.
-All right.
-Yeah.
It's time to start leveling up
on niggas.
I gotta kick off
this European tour.
Shit about to be real different.
Luke really came through
with that one.
-Yeah.
But you should
be headlining that tour.
Yep, I should be...
but I ain't.
ALFRED:
Oh.
All right. I got to...
I got to run some errands
before I meet up at the house,
okay? So, I'll see you there.
-Yeah. The movers
coming by, right?
-Yeah.
You and Darius need to be
packed up. We can't be late.
Yeah, yeah. We know, man.
A'ight, Lottie.
I'll catch up with you, man.
Come on.
-Jewish.
-Yeah.
-Jewish dude, man.
-Yeah, I got you.
(muffled music playing
through headphones)
-Oh.
Here you go.
Two books.
You guys looking for Earn?
Sure is. I'm Kenny.
What's going on?
-Cool. Yeah, yeah.
Is that beer?
No.
Okay.
This way.
All right, guys.
These are the movers.
Uh, um, the bedrooms
are in the back. Okay?
Just hurry up.
We got a plane to catch.
-Okay.
-Please.
-All right, little girl.
Here you go.
You guys packed?
Yeah, bet you think you slick.
What're you talking about?
ALFRED:
Yeah.
-I don't want that thing, man.
-See, you're gonna jam me up.
-Okay, I'm sorry.
All right?
I'll-I'll-I'll get rid of it.
Just throw it in the ocean, bro.
You guys got your passports?
Yeah, but, uh,
Darius gonna need some help.
Oh, yeah, I think mine is, uh,
like, ex-expired or something.
What?
I don't know. It could be just
the date's a little late.
I don't know. Maybe.
Whenever you got guys that don't
know what they're doing.
My nigga,
this is definitely expired.
Don't worry, my friend.
I know a place we can go, get
a renewal same day. It's okay.
Well, we got to do that,
like, today. Right now.
Okay.
: Okay.
It's not that big of a deal.
We'll go.
You think you're slick?
LOTTIE:
They have a penguin.
Monster hat.
All right. Uh, I got to go.
When I get back, we're going
to this passport place.
I'm gonna make sure
that happens, okay?
And Al? Could you, um,
just stay on these guys?
Okay, we got an international
flight, which means we got
to be there early,
and I know you sell weed,
-so you don't care about time...
-True.
...but it's important,
all right?
All right. I'll catch
you guys later. Lottie!
Why did he give me
your passport?
Huh. All right, it's your turn.
Almost there.
Here we go.
All right.
Now we got to...
find the... room.
-No.
Huh?
Okay. Yeah.
Here we...
There we go.
(woman humming to the tune of
"Wheels on the Bus")
I'm sorry. Did we come
at a wrong time?
Oh. No. No, no, no,
not at all.
How are you, Vanessa?
-Nice to see you again.
-Mm-hmm.
And you must be Lottie's father.
-Hi.
So nice to finally meet you.
This is just a conference
I wanted to have
to talk to the both
of you about Lottie.
Is everything all right?
Um... she seems to be...
very... advanced.
Very gifted.
-Oh, my God. Thank God.
I thought
she was pulling her hair out
-and eating it or something.
-Oh. Nothing of the sort.
Or like sniffing Wite-Out
-or something bad.
-Oh, no, no, no.
-Biting children.
-Yeah.
Far from it. Far from it.
She is excelling in everything.
I mean,
she knows all her colors,
she knows her letters.
She's beginning to work
math problems.
-Mmm.
-That's why I spoke
with my friend
at the Holy Oak Academy.
It's one of the best schools
in the Southeast.
They have space available
for their pre-K program
next year,
and I think it might be
a good idea
for the two of you to consider
enrolling Lottie there.
EARN:
Okay.
-Private school, yeah.
It's a private school.
It has a reasonable tuition.
-Okay. Okay.
-Mmm.
Okay, we'll-we'll definitely
do that.
That-That-That sounds like
something we'd-we'd probably do,
-uh, for first grade.
-Get the money together.
Yeah. Is there anything
we can do with her staying here,
to
Like, maybe, um,
some more books or assignments?
Stay here? No.
This school is awful.
-Yes.
There are not enough resources
or faculty
to engage a student like Lottie.
She is really stunting
her education here.
Is there something
we could do for Lottie
that, um...
would be...
...cheaper?
Keep her in a happy,
two
-Huh.
-Hmm.
-Interesting.
-Good.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. It was nice
-seeing you again, Ms. Granger.
-Nice to see you, too.
Thank you.
-VAN: Lottie.
-EARN: Uh, we...
we're gonna go home.
-We're gonna go home.
-Bye!
I'm sorry.
Um...
would you have told us
that this school was bad
if she really was
a regular student?
No.
If I see a steer smart enough
to get out of the pen,
I leave the gate open.
Thank you for coming in.
Thank you.
VAN:
So, she just compared the school
to a slaughterhouse, right?
EARN: Yeah, she definitely did.
I heard that.
VAN:
Okay.
I mean, she's crazy.
Schools in this area
aren't that great. We knew that.
-Lottie, come here.
-Yeah.
-But at least here,
she won't be the only black kid.
I interviewed at Holy Oak's.
It is pretty white, but that's
all these private schools.
-You know that.
You chose Princeton.
Yeah.
LOTTIE:
Mm.
You leaving for,
like, two months?
Yeah, but, you know, that...
that should be tuition
for her now.
LOTTIE:
Mm.
If she goes to this school,
she's gonna need you to show up.
More than you've been able to.
-Yeah, I know. We'll...
we'll make it work.
Get in the car, baby.
I was...
-Under the bridge.
-Let me help.
Oh, watch your head.
Oh, it's a big one.
-You know, I always thought
she was gonna be smart.
-LOTTIE: That's it.
I think
every parent thinks that.
I don't know. I mean...
I thought she was, like,
gonna actually be advanced.
You're smart.
I figured...
some of it
would get passed along,
hopefully.
Yeah, well,
you're smart, too, so...
maybe it was yours, you know?
Thanks.
All right, I got to...
I got to get going.
I got to make sure
Darius gets his passport
-and got to catch this flight.
-Okay.
Be good.
All right?
Be good for Mama. I love you.
-All right.
-See you.
Yeah.
VAN:
You okay?
Oh, yeah. Um...
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just, you know, stupid shit.
It's nothing.
Okay.
Stay safe.
I will. You, too.
-Bye!
-Have fun.
-I will.
-LOTTIE: Hi.
Thank you.
-Yo.
What the hell is going on?
Man, I'm bruisin' this boy.
Who are y'all?
We're Kenny's kids.
EARN:
What are y'all doing here?
DONTRELLE:
School let out.
So?
Man, you sorry.
-I told you you sorry.
-Whoo-wee!
Y'all went to lunch?
We get a lunch break.
It's 3:00 p.m.
Yeah. I didn't eat
before I came.
Oh, yeah. Darius is packed!
I'm ready to go.
Great. Just-just put
your luggage in the car, man.
Oh. No, I meant
I'm packed to move,
not for the airport.
Nigga, it's fine. We'll
just come back here afterwards.
Kenny, I really need you
to pack up everything, man.
Damn. You bruisin' that boy.
-Come on...
-EARN: Yeah, I know,
but now we're late,
and I just need everything
to go.
Can we eat first?
My crew's hungry.
I'll give you 50 more dollars.
Y'all get up off that table.
Dontrelle, grab something
and take it to the truck.
-You, too, Shawn.
-Garbage.
All right. I'll meet you
downstairs, Darius.
I got your passport.
Bring your keys.
Okay. Oh.
Sh-Shit, wait, uh, I think
I might've packed up the keys.
-You are not serious.
-God flabbit.
-I think I did. Um...
-Goddamn it.
No, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Actually...
-Right.
-No, I think I packed... Wait.
Ah!
The old switcheroo.
-Sometimes things just jump
from pocket...
-We need to go!
*
When you piss, do you go
straight through the zipper
or do you go over the boxers?
Over the boxers.
Yeah. Me, too.
But is that the right way,
though?
I don't think so.
Bro, you could...
Yeah.
But, I mean, I do switch it up
when I'm wearing a suit.
You know?
EARN: I didn't even know
this neighborhood existed.
DARIUS:
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-Yep.
YOUNG MAN: Uh,
we'll help you out down here.
Hey. How can I help you guys?
Yeah, we need
a passport replacement.
-Today.
-Yeah.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um,
just, uh, fill out these forms,
and we can make it happen.
All right. Thank you.
I love you.
Thanks.
Really? 'Cause I-I really
thought we were gonna be S.O.L.
Yeah. It's what we do here.
Y'all, uh, going on tour?
Y'all in a rap entourage?
Manager?
How'd you know?
We kind of have a...
specific clientele here. And...
rappers are procrastinators.
No offense.
None taken.
So, who y'all work with?
Uh, Paper Boi.
We're going on tour
with Clark County in Europe.
Oh, man, that's cool. Nice.
I was just listening
to that new Clark joint.
-* Yoo-hoo. * Yeah, yeah.
Oh, man.
Yo, y'all need
an entertainment lawyer?
My cousin is primo.
Uh, I need ID.
Oh. Yeah.
How'd your cousin
get into the business?
Uh, my uncle does it.
Thanks, man.
Let me ask you something.
And, um,
be honest.
Do you think
there's a black lawyer
who's as good as your cousin?
There definitely is.
But, um, part of being good at
your job are your connections,
and black people
just don't have the connections
that my cousin has.
For systemic reasons.
All right.
It's all good.
Oh, perfect.
Yeah, it should be,
like, uh, two hours.
-Oh.
-Cool.
-That's fast.
-Yeah, yeah.
It's, uh, $350.
Oh, that's why. Okay.
Y'all take RushCards?
Yeah, I think so.
DARIUS:
Here you go, my Jewish friend.
-Thank you.
How's it going, Earn?
You doing all right?
Definitely not.
Is Al gonna fire me?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I know you're always at peace
with everything,
but my whole world's
falling apart.
So...
Look, man,
Alfred, his whole world
changing up with the quickness.
Everything's moving, but...
he ain't gonna never forget
to take care of the ones
he's supposed to provide for,
including you.
I don't want a handout.
I got to provide, too.
I'm getting better at this.
You know that.
-No, I know.
-You know.
I see you, man.
I see you... learning.
But...
learning requires failure.
Al just trying to make sure
you ain't failing in...
in his life.
You know, like,
y'all both black, so...
I mean, y'all both
can't afford to fail.
Do Nigerians get a chance
to fail?
Hey, don't you start that.
You know Nigerians don't fail.
Look, whatever he does,
he ain't gonna do it
till we get to Europe.
Give you a chance
to see the world.
How do you know?
Seems like an Al thing to do.
Y'all ready to do this?
Yeah. Darius is coming down,
and I'm calling a Lyft
right now.
Don't you got
to take the truck back?
Kenny's gonna do it.
I offered
to pay him ten dollars.
Can we talk?
Let's talk when we land, man.
(Darius imitates
plane engine buzzing)
Boom.
That's all you're bringing?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, rule number one--
pack like a Navy SEAL.
Only take what you need.
EARN: Lyft'll be here
in three minutes.
(car approaches,
music plays with booming beat)
(car engine
and music playing fade)
No.
Come on. You know you want it.
-EARN: No, I'm all right.
-* Ooh-hoo! *
* Whoo-hoo, whoo-hoo *
* Whoo-hoo, whoo-hoo! *
:
Smoke me!
I really want to be smoked.
: I'm okay.
:
You know you want to smoke me.
: Welcome to
-EARN: Gate C7.
-Atlanta, Hartsfield
International Airport.
-Uh-huh.
See, I told you, Earn.
We was gonna make it.
You just got to learn
to trust yourself, my friend.
We're still late, actually.
She printed our tickets,
but she made sure to say,
"Y'all ain't gonna make it,"
five times
while she was doing it, so we
should probably still hurry.
MAN :
Thank you.
-No, no.
WOMAN :
Elizabeth Battola,
your child is waiting
for you...
CLARK: Oh, shit.
Is that Paper Boi?
What's up, y'all?
-Y'all niggas ready
for this tour?
-Sh... Oh, yeah.
Man, we gonna be poppin' bottles
in Paris, bro.
-It's gonna be crazy. Yeah.
-It's lit, bro.
Speaking sign language to hoes.
-It's gonna be dope, man.
-I'm good, man.
-You check out that lawyer
I sent you?
Hell, yeah, man.
He's perfect. I appreciate it.
Hey, okay, cool.
Let's-let's do this over here.
Flight's not gonna leave
without Clark County, baby.
-Yeah.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
-WOMAN: Please take liquids
-out of your bags...
...and laptops, too.
Place everything in the bins.
-Your pockets should be empty.
-WOMAN 2: Remove your jackets.
:
Opt out!
-MAN: Oh.
You always got to opt out.
Opt for the pat-down, man.
I'm telling you, this-this thing
here-- bad business.
That's why security stays
so close to the food.
They don't want you to smell
your brain frying in this thing.
-WOMAN: Excuse me. Sorry.
WOMAN 2:
Everything in the bins, people.
(sound ceases
except for quiet beeping)
(sound resumes,
indistinct chatter)
Will you hand me a bin?
You got to get it
from the front, man.
Oh, man, he asked nicely.
-Thanks.
(indistinct,
overlapping crowd chatter)
-ALFRED: You know what
I don't get?
How they make you take all your
shit off, and they try to rush
to get you out of the way,
like they ain't just asked me
-to take all your shit off
ten seconds ago.
ALFRED: That's why I fuckin'
hate the airport, man.
DARIUS:
Yeah, it's not efficient.
-ALFRED: All that shit isn't.
-We should hurry.
-All right.
Hey, what
What's going on?
WOMAN:
We're going this way.
We're starting another line
this way.
CLARK:
Hey, yo, Luke, come here.
Man, this trip
gonna be crazy, boy.
I mean, I ain't never really
left Georgia before, so, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's gonna be cool.
Yeah, it'll be cool.
-Shit.
Yeah.
-WOMAN 2: Yes, ma'am.
WOMAN: Okay, I'm just gonna
move this over here
to make a little more room.
I saw what you did...
-at TSA.
-Mm.
You ain't got to say shit.
Just know that's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Niggas do not care about us,
man.
Niggas gonna do whatever
they got to do to survive,
'cause they ain't got no choice.
We ain't got no choice, either.
You my family, Earn.
Yeah, you...
You're the only one
that knows what I'm about.
You give a fuck.
I need that.
All right?
All right, then.
Hey?
Let's get this money.
BOTH:
Brrr!
-Hey, shit.
-Yeah, boy.
ALFRED:
Hey, Clark, man?
Let me holler at you.
Yeah. What's up, man?
Where Luke at, man?
Uh, nah, man.
Luke got in some shit.
Cops took him.
ALFRED:
What you talking about?
TSA found a tool in his bag.
Damn.
-Oh.
-It's just kind of...
Oh, he probably had
a screwdriver or something.
You can't have those on a plane.
Yeah. More like a hammer.
Yeah. It was gold, too.
Shit was clean, though.
Wish it was mine.
* Yoohoo! *
The piece was in Clark's bag.
-*
-TRACY: Yo, Alf!
Yo, open the door, man!
Open up, man!
Listen, man, I got Chinese food
with a side of chocolate.
!
Is this mother...?
Al, man,
-stop playing, bro. Let me in!
-WOMAN: Shut the fuck up!
Hey, you shut the fuck up!
The hell you talking to?
-Ready to whoop your ass.
-Hey! Wake up, niggas!
-* So I remember everything *
Alfred, will you open
the goddamn door?!
-* Of every man *
-* Ooh, ooh *
* Who put me here *
* Oh-oh *
* I see my light come shining *
* From the west down *
* To the east... *
* Any day, now *
* Any day,
now *
* I shall be released *
* They say every man needs
protection *
* They say
every man must fall. *
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH